in this video I'm going to demonstrate
how you can use the slide master view to
make changes to one slate which will
then be applied to every subsequent
slate that you insert into the
presentation so what I need to do is I
need another gate up to the View tab and
under view tab I would need a select
slate master so that's an X late master
that will take me into slate master view
now don't worry too much that all of the
information from your original
presentation isn't visible it is
actually still there all this is doing
is its defining the content the layout
the design the fonts the background
images and the theme that you may be
using or wish to use for each
presentation so one of the things to
remember is that if you wish to make a
change that will be applied to all
slates you need to select slide 1 now
I'm going to insert the company logo and
so our selected slide 1 and all I need
to do then is go to the insert tab
select picture from this device navigate
to the image double click on the image
and it inserts it into the slate I can
just move that up to the top and then
I'll resize that make it quite small and
I'll also change the transparency so
it's very clear and I'm happy with that
again if I make a change to the font so
if I change the font there if I go to
the Home tab and it Calibri late
headings 44 at the moment if I change
that to Arial and see 54 when I come out
of the slide mater so I have to click on
the slide master tab again and close for
slate master view that will
automatically change the size of the
font and as you can also see the image
has been placed at the top of every
slate within the presentation if I go to
a new slate and select a blank slate
again another tail slate it
automatically adds up and the font is
automatically going to be Arial size 60
so if I go back to the view and select
slide master again
go back to slate one I can also change
the theme so if I decided that I wasn't
happy with the theme that I had and I
wanted to change it for all slides in
the presentation and all subsequent
slate I could select a theme that I was
happy with and then from there once I've
got that I could then close the master
view and again that will change the
theme for every slide in the
presentation